<oai_dc:dc xmlns:oai_dc="http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/2.0/oai_dc/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/2.0/oai_dc/ http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/2.0/oai_dc.xsd">
      <dc:title>Museums and memory [electronic resource] /</dc:title>
      <dc:creator>Huber, Margaret Williamson.</dc:creator>
      <dc:creator>Shanafelt, Robert,</dc:creator>
      <dc:creator>Southern Anthropological Society.</dc:creator>
      <dc:type>text</dc:type>
      <dc:type>Electronic books.</dc:type>
      <dc:publisher>Knoxville, Tenn. : Newfound Press, University of Tennessee Libraries,</dc:publisher>
      <dc:date>c2011.</dc:date>
      <dc:language>eng</dc:language>
      <dc:description>"Selected papers from the Annual Meeting of the Southern Anthropological Society, Staunton, Virginia, Mar. 2008" - screen t.p.</dc:description>
      <dc:description>"Southern Anthropological Society" -- screen t.p. verso.</dc:description>
      <dc:description>Introduction / Margaret Williamson Huber -- Forget Culture, Remember Memory? (Keynote Address) / Eric Gable and Richard Handler -- Pests in the Garden: Testing the Garden-Hunting Model at the Rutherford-Kizer Site, Sumner County, Tennessee / Jennifer Clinton and Tanya M. Peres -- Remembering New Deal Archaeology in the Southeast: A Legacy in Museum Collections / Lynne P. Sullivan, Bobby R. Braly, Michaelyn S. Harle, and Shannon D. Koerner -- Memory within a University Landscape / Laura J. Galke and Bernard K. Means -- Memorialization and Living History in Chartering the Nation: Perspectives on the Frontier Culture Museum in Staunton, Virginia / Alison Bell and Parker Wolf -- The Jamestown Commemoration of 2007: Remembering our Diversity in the Past and Present / Vincent H. Melomo -- Vandalizing Meaning, Stealing Memory: Thoughts on Crime in Galleries and Museums / Avi Brisman -- Menace and Majesty: the Jocassee Gorges Region of Upper South Carolina / John M. Coggeshall -- Miss Lillibelle, Moonshine, and Midnight at the Crystal Café: Remembrances of a Southeast Arkansas Culture-scape / Susan Elizabeth Probasco -- Objects of Desire: Photographs and Retrospective Narratives of Fieldwork in Indonesia / Jennifer W. Nourse -- Memory and Celebration in Contemporary San Miguel de Allende, Mexico / Samantha Krause -- Moving Around in the Room: Cherokee Language, Worldview and Memory / Heidi Altman and Tom Belt.</dc:description>
      <dc:description>Title from PDF title page (Newfound Press Web site, viewed on Oct. 11, 2011).</dc:description>
      <dc:description>Includes bibliographical references.</dc:description>
      <dc:subject>Historical museums</dc:subject>
      <dc:relation>Also available print-on-demand at publisher's website.</dc:relation>
      <dc:identifier>http://www.newfoundpress.utk.edu/pubs/museums/</dc:identifier>
      <dc:identifier>http://utpress.org/bookdetail-2/?jobno=T01630</dc:identifier>
      <dc:identifier>URN:ISBN:0984644520 (electronic bk.) -- Canceled or invalid ISBN</dc:identifier>
      <dc:identifier>URN:ISBN:9780984644520 (electronic bk.) -- Canceled or invalid ISBN</dc:identifier>
      <dc:identifier>DOI:10.7290/V7H41PBD</dc:identifier>
   </oai_dc:dc>
